here with Broncos assistant general
manager Reed Birkhart. Reed, the uh 2026
NFL draft just wrapped up and you guys
started off with a a flurry of moves at
the start of day three. George Payton
said yesterday that those first couple
of day, excuse me, round four picks
could set the tone for this draft. Ended
up drafting Jonah Coleman out of
Washington, Cage Casey out of Boise
State. What' you see with those two guys
and and what do they add to this roster?
>> What's interesting, he said it was going
to set the tone because those are two
tone setters. Um Jonah, you know, is a
physical downhill runner. fits our
style, fits what we have uh in our
running back group right now. And then
and then Cage is is a physical high
makeup, high trait player um that really
gonna fit in our old line room and and
we talk about setting the tone for our
team in the offensive line room and and
he certainly is going to add to that.
>> Justin Jolie, then you guys trade up to
get him. What was it about him that made
you guys want to move up the board to
add him to this roster?
>> Well, fits the theme with with the first
two. He's a highly competitive kid. We
we really liked our top 30 visit with
him. just liked how he carried himself
in the building around our coaches,
around our staff. Really felt his
infectiousness, uh his energy, uh his
competitiveness, and he's got a pass
game skill set, and so we were really
excited to get him because of all those
things.
>> Sean then mentioned it was a long wait
until you guys picked again in round
seven, but uh added three guys and Miles
Scott, Don Bentley, and then Red Murdoch
there with the Mr. Irrelevant pick. What
were those final minutes of the draft
like as you were able to add three guys
who could potentially contribute to this
team? Well, when you get to that point,
you're hoping they're there, you know,
and at that point, everyone's board
looks different and so they're coming
from from all different angles and and
and to get miles um and to add to our
safety depth. Uh he was a receiver that
converted to to safety and his first
year at safety. He started three years
started at Illinois and we got a little
inside information uh from Palo and and
Pat and um man, they were bringing him
up to us. He came on a 30 and they were
like, "Man, we got to get this guy. We
got to get this guy." So, high respect
for for those two players and the
program they played in and and see that
extending with with Miles. And then Don,
you know, had a really productive year
this year at Utah. Um little bit
different play style than Justin. Um a
little bit more of an inline wide,
bigger body, but um like his upside and
then with Red, you know, really
productive year at Buffalo. Uh he was
ball production, uh forced fumbles, he's
always around the ball, special teams
upside. So, he's going to fit well in
that group as well and really plays to
the style that that our defense plays
to.
>> Re, as you look back on the last three
days, I'm not a pick on round one, but
you did add Jaylen Wadd to this roster
last month. Just how would you evaluate
overall this draft class and how it can
help this team moving forward?
>> Well, I I think the central theme to
this draft class is is the things that
we touched on with the competitiveness.
Uh they fit our culture. all the all
these guys, they're going to raise the
level uh when they come in and add to
our current group and and they're going
to fit right in, you know, and so um
when we can add to the collective, uh we
feel really good about it.
>> Reed, appreciate your time and
congratulations on another strong draft.
>> All right. Thank you.